thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
Nice, open-air bath.
いいね、露天風呂ね
I wish it were in this house.
この家にあったらいいですね
The best.
最 高
Girls like taking baths.
女の子はお風呂好きだもんね
Why girls?
なんで女子は?
When I look at you in the bathtub, you look like Shizuka-chan.
湯船に浸かっているあなたを見ていると静かちゃんみたいだね
It feels like Shizuka-chan.
静かちゃんっぽい感じがするよ
What is it?
なんだろう?
She's a super quiet character.
超静かちゃんキャラですよ
Try telling me to drink it.
飲み出さんって言ってみて
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じですよ
Is your body warm?
体は温まっていますか?
Yeah.
うん
Please, please.
お願い なんですけど
please.
お願い
Look at Shizuka-chan's urination.
静かちゃんの 放尿を見てみて
Pissing?
放尿?
quiet?
静か?
I understand, right?
分かっているじゃないですか
Pissing pee.
放尿おしっこ
That's it.
あれですよ
You can't do it here.
ここでやっちゃダメですよ
The problem is the altitude.
問題高度ですからね
Do you understand?
分かります?
Here's me peeing, here's another bonus.
ここに来て おしっこをしているところを これも おまけに
I will.
します よ
It's quite amazing, isn't it?
なかなかすごいじゃないですか
Just half a step ahead.
もうちょっと半歩前
This is pee, but does it have a smell?
これ、おしっこすなんですけど においってあります?
Smell?
におい?
be.
ある
Have you ever peed in public?
人前でおしっこしたことある?
be.
ある
Then you can do it.
じゃあできるんじゃん
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Because it's zooming.
ズームするからさ
yes.
はい
When you tell me.
教えてくれるとき
good?
いい?
Pee, pee.
おしっこ、おしっこ
Can you stop it?
止めれる?
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
This time, I want a stroke.
今度はせっかくなんで ストロークが欲しいじゃん
So, put your feet here and here, and put your feet in front of you like this.
だから、ここと こっち足を置いて 前の方にさ 両足をこう置
Do you understand?
いて 手後ろに ついて 分かる?
This is a little bit. What do you think will happen if you pee in this?
これでちょっとさ これでおしっこしたらどうなると思う?
can?
できる?
Did it come out?
出ちゃった?
That's the case around here.
この 辺そうだ
この辺そうだよ
That's the case around here.
Around here.
この辺
It's pee.
おしっこだよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Thank you for letting me know your precious honest thoughts.
貴重な 貴重な本音を 見ていただきまして、
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Let's take a commemorative photo.
記念撮ってきましょう
This shaved pussy.
このパイパンマンコーマ
It smells good.
いい匂いする
It will last a long time even outdoors.
屋外でも ずーんとしますよ
Ammonia.
アンモニアが